export const flashcards = [
    { id: 1, question: 'What continent is Bhutan in?', answer: 'Asia' },
    { id: 2, question: 'What continent is Suriname in?', answer: 'South America' },
    { id: 3, question: 'What continent is Djibouti in?', answer: 'Africa' },
    { id: 4, question: 'What continent is Andorra in?', answer: 'Europe' },
    { id: 5, question: 'What continent is Vanuatu in?', answer: 'Australia' },
    { id: 6, question: 'What continent is Lesotho in?', answer: 'Africa' },
    { id: 7, question: 'What continent is Brunei in?', answer: 'Asia' },
    { id: 8, question: 'What continent is Guyana in?', answer: 'South America' },
    { id: 9, question: 'What continent is Moldova in?', answer: 'Europe' },
    { id: 10, question: 'What continent is Timor-Leste in?', answer: 'Asia' },
  ];
  
